For National, the premium has
seen an increase of around 18%.
In two minimas, the premium is increasing by around 19%.
This is an update for general insurance companies.
In Standard Health Insurance, the
MAP premium has seen an increase of up to 23%
and in two minimas, the
free of charge fee is 28% bigger. Let's
start with ICC Lombard, where here
we are seeing a rise of around 21% in the MAP premium.
In two minimas, there is an increase of around 18%.
However, the market share has decreased by 10-20 points.
In New India Insurance, the
premium has increased by 10% in the last month. This premium has
seen an increase of only 10% in the last two minimas
and they have made a significant loss in the market share of
around 1.5%.
New India Insurance is making a loss. Whereas,
if you pay attention to Star Health, a rise of 16% has been
seen in the premium in the last month.
In the last two minimas, there is a rise of 20%
in the premium
and their mother charge is very high.  Main rise increasing
.0 3% So these are in fact data points derived
from the insurance companies. The
views given by the experts are their own personal
views. Do not
take advice from the website.